// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I have lost ……………… pen you lent me.",
    answer: "the",
    options: [ "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Let's watch ……………… movie.",
    answer: "both of above with different contexts",
    options: ["a","the","both of above with different contexts","no article"]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"The cow is ………………… very useful animal.",
    answer: "a",
    options: [
      "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Sam is …………………… brightest student in ………… class.",
    answer: "the,the",
    options: ["a,the","an,the","the,the","a,a" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "This is ………………… biggest city I have ever visited.",
    answer: "the",
    options: [ "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Armstrong was ……………… first man to walk on the moon.",
    answer: "the",
    options: ["a", "an","the","no article"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "…………………. last chapter of this book is very exciting.",
    answer: "the",
    options: [ "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "………………… man is mortal.",
    answer: "no article",
    options: [ "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "……………… life is complicated.",
    answer: "no article",
    options: [ "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What kind of ………………… fruit is this?",
    answer: "no article",
    options: [  "a", "an","the","no article"  ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "Give me ………………… call when you are ready.",
    answer: "a",
    options: [  "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: " ………………… rich are getting richer.",
    answer: "the",
    options: [  "a", "an","the","no article" ]
  },
];